http://www.watrust.com/support/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyWhat does Washington Trust Bank do with your personal information?Why?Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.What?The types of personal information we collect and share depends on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:Social Security number and account balancestransaction history and payment historycredit history and checking account informationWhen you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.How?All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Washington Trust Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Washington Trust Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharingReasons we can share your personal informationDoes Washington Trust Bank share?Can you limit this sharing?For our everyday business purposes— such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureausYESNOFor our marketing purposes— to offer our products and services to youYESNOFor joint marketing with other financial companiesNOWe don’t shareFor our affiliates’ everyday business purposes— information about your transactions and experiencesNOWe don’t shareFor our affiliates’ everyday business purposes— information about your creditworthinessNOWe don’t shareFor nonaffiliates to market to youNOWe don’t shareQuestions? Call 800.788.4578 or go to www.watrust.com.questions and answers regarding Washington Trust Bank's sharing of personal informationQuestionAnswerHow does Washington Trust Bank protect my personal information?To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.How does Washington Trust Bank collect my personal information?We collect your personal information, for example, when youopen an account or deposit moneypay your bills or apply for a loanuse your debit card or credit cardWe also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.Why can’t I limit all sharing?Federal law gives you the right to limit onlysharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthinessaffiliates from using your information to market to yousharing for nonaffiliates to market to youState laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.DefinitionsAffiliates: Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.Washington Trust Bank does not share with our affiliate.Nonaffiliates: Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.Washington Trust Bank does not share customer information with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.Joint marketing: A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.Washington Trust Bank does not jointly market.
